[{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663890174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":11382,"timeElapsed":55068},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663893984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3808,"timeElapsed":58878},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663899170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5185,"timeElapsed":64064},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663907865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":8693,"timeElapsed":72758},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663915511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7645,"timeElapsed":80405},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663923399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7887,"timeElapsed":88293},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663927785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4385,"timeElapsed":92679},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663935503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7717,"timeElapsed":100397},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663941044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5539,"timeElapsed":105937},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663970408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":27971,"timeElapsed":135302},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663973558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3149,"timeElapsed":138452},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663978534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4975,"timeElapsed":143428},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663986201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":7665,"timeElapsed":151095},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663990955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4753,"timeElapsed":155849},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663997441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6485,"timeElapsed":162335},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664001053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3611,"timeElapsed":165947},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664008099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7045,"timeElapsed":172993},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664012029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3929,"timeElapsed":176923},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664024070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9970,"timeElapsed":188964},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664026648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2577,"timeElapsed":191542},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664031495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4847,"timeElapsed":196389},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664038400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6903,"timeElapsed":203294},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664041720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3319,"timeElapsed":206614},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664048418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6697,"timeElapsed":213312},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664052842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4423,"timeElapsed":217736},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664057763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4919,"timeElapsed":222656},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664060364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2601,"timeElapsed":225258},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664162241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":100630,"timeElapsed":327135},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664165863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3621,"timeElapsed":330757},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664180268,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14403,"timeElapsed":345161},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664187382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7113,"timeElapsed":352275},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664192398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5015,"timeElapsed":357292},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664195170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2771,"timeElapsed":360064},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664200242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5071,"timeElapsed":365136},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2389,"timeElapsed":367526},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664208142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5509,"timeElapsed":373036},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664211265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3121,"timeElapsed":376159},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664220868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8401,"timeElapsed":385762},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664222997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2127,"timeElapsed":387891},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664227061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4063,"timeElapsed":391955},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664232157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5095,"timeElapsed":397051},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664235135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2977,"timeElapsed":400029},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664238575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3439,"timeElapsed":403469},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2953,"timeElapsed":406423},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4239,"timeElapsed":410663},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664248887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3117,"timeElapsed":413781},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":8197,"timeElapsed":423050},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664261380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3223,"timeElapsed":426274},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3305,"timeElapsed":429579},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4105,"timeElapsed":433686},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2746,"timeElapsed":436432},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664274888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":439782},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2899,"timeElapsed":442682},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4219,"timeElapsed":446902},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664283994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1985,"timeElapsed":448888},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664290806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5630,"timeElapsed":455700},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664293896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3089,"timeElapsed":458790},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664298365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4467,"timeElapsed":463259},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3947,"timeElapsed":467206},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6271,"timeElapsed":473479},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4487,"timeElapsed":477967},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316585,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3512,"timeElapsed":481479},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5197,"timeElapsed":486677},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664324325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2541,"timeElapsed":489219},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3133,"timeElapsed":492353},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10316,"timeElapsed":503673},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3959,"timeElapsed":507633},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2897,"timeElapsed":510532},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":10807,"timeElapsed":521340},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664362288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5841,"timeElapsed":527182},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6427,"timeElapsed":533610},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2227,"timeElapsed":535838},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2255,"timeElapsed":538095},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2413,"timeElapsed":540508},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5323,"timeElapsed":547232},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664385263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2924,"timeElapsed":550157},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664388103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2838,"timeElapsed":552997},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6243,"timeElapsed":559241},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664397045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2697,"timeElapsed":561939},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664402037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4992,"timeElapsed":566931},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664404567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2529,"timeElapsed":569461},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664408088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3520,"timeElapsed":572981},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664410587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2499,"timeElapsed":575481},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664419802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8151,"timeElapsed":584696},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2553,"timeElapsed":587249},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4813,"timeElapsed":592064},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664433192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6021,"timeElapsed":598086},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664437426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4233,"timeElapsed":602320},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664443098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5671,"timeElapsed":607992},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2561,"timeElapsed":610555},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4495,"timeElapsed":615050},{"subjectID":"f2ko3nlfyz","prolificID":"669fe153448a8b15cf4b12e2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420b8a5cc6549e7d8cecd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664452566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2409,"timeElapsed":617460}]